&gt；&gt；Speaker 1：我们一直在讨论编译阶段的函数，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: We've been talking about functions in the compilation phase,
将其标识符作为彩色大理石添加到封闭范围中。
adding their identifier as a colored marble in the enclosing scope.
在这个例子中，我们有一个函数老师在一号线上，
In this example, we have a function teacher on line one,
老师会是什么颜色的大理石？
what color marble is teacher gonna be?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：红色。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Red.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：红色，好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Red, okay.
但是让我们看看第三行，因为行看起来有点不同。
But let's look at line three because line looks a little bit different.
第三行可能看起来更像一些函数，
And line three might look a little bit more like some of the functions that
你见过更常见的。
you've seen more commonly.
也许看到老式的功能装饰会比较少见，
It's maybe a little less common to see the old school function decoration,
虽然我强烈喜欢功能装饰只是为了记录。
although I strongly prefer function decorations just for the record.
但现在大多数人似乎喜欢声明变量和
But most people seem to like these days to declare variables and
为它们分配函数，通常它们甚至使用常量而不是var。
assign functions to them and usually they even use a constant instead of a var.
所以这可能看起来有点像你最近看到的。
So that might look a little bit like what you've seen recently.
所以那里发生了什么
So what's happening there and
这和一号线的情况有什么不同吗？
is it any different than what's happening with line one?
好的，请记住，在编译时可能发生的事情之间是有区别的
Well, remember, there is a difference between what can happen at compile time
以及在执行时会发生什么。
and what can happen at execution time.
因此，我们知道将创建一个名为myTeacher的标识符，并且
So, we do know that an identifier called myTeacher is going to be created and
它会是什么颜色的大理石？
what color marble is it gonna be?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：红色。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Red.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：它将是红色的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: It's gonna be red.
我们知道那里有一个叫做另一个Teacher的函数，所以
We do know that there's a function called anotherTeacher there, so
我们至少需要为它创建一个桶。
we need to create a bucket for it at least.
我们需要做一个蓝色的桶。
We need to make a blue bucket.
但因为该函数不是声明，
But because that function is not a declaration,
我们不会以同样的方式处理它的大理石颜色。
we're not gonna handle its marble color in the same way.
这里的关键区别是另一个教师标识符，
The key difference here is that the anotherTeacher identifier,
第三行的这个标识符将会变成一个大理石
the one right here on line three, that identifier is going to end up as a marble
在编译时，但是它将是一个不同于你预期的颜色的大理石。
at compile time but it's gonna be a different colored marble than you expect.
这不是红色的大理石，是蓝色的大理石。
It's not a red marble, it's a blue marble.
所以这里有一个关键的区别。
So there is a key difference here.
这称为与行相反的函数表达式，
This is called a function expression as opposed to what line one is,
称为函数声明。
is called a function declaration.
关键的区别之一，我们将在整个课程中看到更多，但是
And one of the key differences, and we'll see more throughout the course but
函数声明和函数之间的关键区别之一
one of the key differences between function declarations and
函数表达式，即函数声明及其名称，
function expressions, is that function declarations and their name,
他们把他们的大理石贴在围栏上，所以我们在一号线上做了一个红色的大理石
they attach their marble to the enclosing scope, so we make a red marble on line one
而函数表达式会将它们的大理石添加到它们自己的范围中。
whereas function expressions will add their marble to their own scope.
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：那么蓝色范围就是蓝色大理石和另一个教师结束的地方。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So the blue scope is where the blue marble anotherTeacher ends up.
&gt；&gt；演讲者1：这就是为什么在第四行，我们可以引用另一个讲师，因为
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: That's why on line four, we can reference in anotherTeacher because
事实上，有一种蓝色的大理石叫做另一种老师。
there is in fact a blue marble called anotherTeacher.
但是在九号线下，没有另一个老师，是吗？
But down on line nine, there is no anotherTeacher, is there?
当我们在全球范围内
When we're out in the global scope and
我们问全球范围你听说过这个红色大理石吗，它会说没有，
we asked global scope you ever heard of this red marble, it's gonna say nope,
从来没有听说过那个红色的大理石，我们会得到什么，参考错误。
never heard of that red marble and what we're gonna get there, reference error.
所以关键差异，函数表达式，
So key difference, function expressions,
把你的身份放在自己的范围内。
put there identify your into their own scope.
有一点细微的差别。
There's a little nuance.
让我一会儿来回答这个问题。
Let me get to that question in a moment.
此外，还有一些额外的细微差别，不仅是蓝色
There's a little, also, additional nuance which is not only does that blue
大理石显示在蓝色范围内，但它也是只读的。
marble show up in the blue scope but it's also read only.
您不能在第四行重新分配另一位教师。
You cannot reassign anotherTeacher on line four.
您不能将其重新分配给其他值。
You could not reassign it to some other value.
你有问题是吗？
You have a question, yes?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：你为什么要这么做？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Why would you do this?
为什么实际上在右侧有命名的函数
Why would you actually have the named function on the right side of
那个表情？
that expression?
&gt；&gt；Speaker 1：您可能更经常看到它是一个匿名函数，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: You've probably more often seen it as an anonymous function there,
我们将讨论所谓的命名函数之间的区别
and we're about to discuss the difference between what are so-called named function
表达式，以及更常见的匿名函数表达式。
expressions, and the more common anonymous function expression.
好的，我们一会儿就会讲到这一点。
Okay, so we'll get into that in just a moment.
很棒的片段，让我们来讨论命名函数表达式。
So great segue, let's talk about named function expressions.
什么是命名函数表达式？
What is a named function expression?
我们超级有创造力，
We're super creative,
这意味着一个已经被命名的函数表达式，好吗？
that means a function expression that's been given a name, okay?
那么让我们来看看这两个。
So let's look at these two.
第一行，我声明一个函数表达式。
Line one, I'm declaring a function expression.
为什么它是函数表达式？
Why is it a function expression?
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：它被赋值给一个变量？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's assigned to a variable?
&gt；&gt；Speaker 1：因为它不是函数声明，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Because it's not a function declaration,
我们如何知道某件事是不是函数声明
how do we know if something's a function declaration
如果单词function是语句中的第一件事？
if the word function is literally the first thing in the statement?
所以如果它不是语句中的第一件事，如果有一个变量或
So if it's not the first thing in the statement, if there's a variable or
一个运算符或圆括号或任何东西，那么它不是一个声明，是吗？
an operator or parentheses or anything, then it's not a declaration, it is?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：表达式。&gt；&gt；扬声器1：表达式，所以
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: An expression. &gt;&gt; Speaker 1: An expression, so
在第一行，我们看到一个函数表达式，但我们看不到名称。
on line one, we see a function expression, but we see no name.
这就是所谓的匿名函数表达式，
So that's called a anonymous function expression,
而第五行上的是一个命名的函数表达式。
whereas the one on line five is a named function expression.
所以撇开函数表达式和
So setting aside the difference between function expressions and
声明一下。
declarations for a moment.
在这里，我只想把我们的注意力集中在
Here, I just wanna focus our attention to the difference between
匿名函数表达式和命名函数表达式。
anonymous function expressions and named function expressions.
我要说的是即使匿名函数
And what I'm gonna claim is that even though anonymous function
表达方式要普遍得多，事实上也要流行得多，
expressions are vastly more common, vastly more popular In fact,
你们中的大多数人可能从未见过命名的函数表达式。
most of you have maybe never even seen a named function expression.
这就是它是多么的不常见和不受欢迎。
And that's how uncommon and unpopular it is.
我要提出的主张是，你应该总是，100%，零例外。
I'm going to make the claim that you should always, 100%, zero exception.
我不会做很多绝对的，100%的陈述，
I don't make very many statements that are that absolute, 100%,
零例外，您应该首选命名函数表达式，
zero exceptions, you should prefer the named function expression,
在匿名函数表达式上。
over the anonymous function expression.